Contact

anitastamos@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anitastamatopoulos-rn-2a704b53 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Clinical Research Home Care

Languages

Greek

Honors-Awards

Hammond Award for Clinical Excellance

Academic Excellence Nursing Award

Anita Stamatopoulos RN

Director of Nursing

Greater Detroit Area

Summary

Experienced Director Of Nursing with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Disease Management, Nursing Education, Medicaid, and Palliative Care. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from School Craft College.

Experience

The Gilbert Residence Assisted Living and Nursing Care Director of Nursing

April 2015 - Present (5 years 4 months)

203 South Huron Street Ypsilanti, MI 48197-5452

Oversee the administrative function of the Nursing Department in concert with the Administrator

Expert Nurse Consulting

Nurse consultant / Professional Expert WItness September 2012 - Present (7 years 11 months)

Ann Arbor, Mlchigan

Legal Nurse Consultants apply their knowledge and understanding of medical,nursing and health-related issues to make an attorney's job easier,more efficient and more effective.

Evangelical Homes of Michigan Senior Case Manager Saline August 2014 - April 2015 (9 months)

Ciena Healthcare Regency of Canton Director of Nursing January 2013 - July 2014 (1 year 7 months)

Canton. Michigan

Oversee the Administrative function of the Nursing Department.

Heartland Healthcare Ann Arbor

Page 1 of 3

Director of Nursing
July 2008 - January 2012 (3 years 7 months)

4701 East Huron River Drive Ann Arbor Michigan

Oversee the administrative functions of Heartland Healthcare's nursing department in concert with the Administrator. Maintain quality standards in accordance with Federal, State, and HCR Manor care standards, guidelines and regulations.

Heartland Healthcare of Ann Arbor

3 years 2 months

Case manager

November 2006 - November 2008 (2 years 1 month)

Provide a range of services, including skilled nursing care, assisted living, post acute medical and rehabilitation care, hospice care, and home health care. Negotiated with insurance representatives, coordinated interdisciplinary plans of care, and assessed patient clinical needs. Managed all secondary insurance cases.

MDS Cordinator

October 2005 - November 2006 (1 year 2 months)

Ensuring that the documentation in the center meets Federal, State, and Certification guidelines. RAI process assuring accuracy, timeliness and completeness of the MDS, RAPS, and interdisplinary Care plan; Further conducted the nursing process of Assessment, Planning, implementation, and Evaluation under the State's Nurse Practice Act.

Heartland of Ann Arbor

RN

May 1998 - May 2005 (7 years 1 month)

Ann Arbor Michigan

Staff Nurse

Garden City Hospital

RN

May 1998 - May 1999 (1 year 1 month)

Garden City Hospital

Contingent RN Floor nurse

Education

School Craft College